

# YAREN NUR SOLMAZ









https://github.com/YNS2121

# **Objective**

I have a strong tendency for a career in game development in a mobil game sector. To be sure, I'd like to experience the actual work environment. I hope that this internship will provide me a realistic ciew of the profession together with the behaviors and skilld necessary for success.

#### **Education**

Firat University Computer Engineering 10/2020-2024 Nuri Erbak Anadolu Lisesi 2016-2020

# **Projects**

- 'Super Meet Boy Game Clone' in Emeltek Software for internship project
- 'Square' game with Unity in MagaraJam#5 (in first 60th) ( https://magarajam.com/game/1203388585634432000 )
- 'Pourckat' game with Unity in IEEE Firat Game Dev. Team ( https://github.com/IEEEFiratComputerSociety/Pourckat )
- 'TravelApp' aplication with Java in IEEE Firat Mobile App. Team ( https://github.com/IEEEFiratComputerSociety/TravelApp )

## **Experience**

 Organizer and social media manager in GDG&WTM Elazig 2020-21 I organized events about technology and moderated youtube also I was responsible the instagram post design and announcement of the events.

Vice Presedent in IEEE Firat Computer Science 2021-22

I orginazed events about computer science and I managed 6 project team (web prog., mobile app. in Flutter, game dev., image processing, desktop app with Java, cyber security team).

• Central Anatolia area responsible in IEEE Turkey Computer Science 2021-22

I was in charge of the organization of events across Turkey. I was managed and helping the club presidents of universities in Central Anatolia.

YetGen

### Work **Experience**

- Game Developer Internship in Emeltek Software /Elazig 08.2022-20 day I was developer Super Meet Boy clone mobile game and I developed my game development skills. I learned internship process. My work as intern was found effective by the management and I was offered extension as part-time developer.
- Social media maneger in @deepoceancode instagram page as volunteer for exprerience

### Skills / **Hobbies**

- Java
- MS Office
- Active Learning
- Acting 'Safinaz'ın İzdivacı' theatre show in highscool 2019
- Folk dance show in Osmangazi Folk Group 2018

